ohiolink.edu 2016-11-26

# Privacy Notice | OH-TECH.org

This web site, a service provided by the Ohio Technology Consortium (the research and technology arm of the Ohio Department of Higher Education, formerly the Ohio Board of Regents), recognizes the importance of privacy to our web site visitors. Therefore, visitors should be aware of the following information.

### Public Records

Visitors should be aware that, subject to certain statutory exceptions, most documents and records maintained by the state of Ohio, including but not limited to electronic data, are public records under Ohio law. Therefore, information submitted through this web site may be subject to disclosure pursuant to a public records request.

### Usage Statistics

In order to generate usage statistics to help us improve our web site, we automatically collect certain information on every visitor to the web site. However, this information does not disclose "personal identifiers" (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc.). Each time a request is made to view a page within this web site, our web site creates a log file capturing generic user information. Examples of this type of information includes the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using, the date and time you accessed this site, the Internet protocol address of the individual computer (or proxy server) making the request, and the Internet address of the site from which you may have linked to this site.

All information collected by way of server log files is used in aggregate form only and may be analyzed for trends and statistics.

### Online Forms and E-mail

This web site will not collect personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, etc.), unless you provide such information voluntarily. We may ask for such information so that we can tailor interactive features of this web site to your specific interests and needs (including periodically forwarding information that matches your selected interests). You are free to provide or not to provide the requested information. If you choose not to provide this type of information, you still can visit most of the web site, but you may be unable to participate in certain online forums. Any personal information voluntarily provided by visitors, including personal information submitted on online forms and e-mail, will be used for the purposes stated on the web page and may also be shared with other agencies as required by law or pursuant to agency authority. Information submitted through this web site also may be subject to disclosure pursuant to a public records request.

### Web Cookies

Visitors who submit information via this web site should be aware that data linking your computer to this web site (a "cookie") might be created. Temporary cookies may be used when necessary to complete a transaction, to process data submitted to us online or to facilitate ongoing Internet interaction. Information collected on our web sites, including cookies, may also be subject to disclosure pursuant to a public records request.

### Security Measures

This web site will follow Ohio state laws that require the establishment of reasonable precautions to prevent personal information from unauthorized modification, destruction, use or disclosure. We take very seriously the integrity of the information and systems that we maintain. Therefore, we have instituted security measures for all information systems under our control. These security measures are designed to identify attempts to tamper with this web site. Information collected through these security measures may be used in connection with a criminal prosecution or other legal proceedings.

### Confidential Personal Information

The Ohio Technology Consortium is the technology arm of the Ohio Department of Higher Education. Ohio Revised Code 1347.15 requires the Ohio Department of Higher Education to adopt administrative rules regulating access to the confidential personal information the agency keeps, whether electronically or on paper. The administrative rules for the Ohio Department of Higher Education may be found [here](http://codes.ohio.gov/oac/3333-1). The Department of Higher Education policy on protecting the privacy of personal information may be found [here](https://www.oh-tech.org/sites/oh-tech.org/files/Policy_On_Protecting_Privacy_feb2015.pdf).

### Access and Dispute of Information Rights

Pursuant to Ohio Revised Code, sections 149.43, 1347.08 and 1347.09, users have rights to their information given to this site, in respect to inspecting, correcting and disputing. This is applicable to any information collected, used or maintained on this website.

### Link Policy

The Ohio Technology Consortium operates this web site as a public service to Ohio residents and visitors worldwide. The web site provides links to external websites that are not maintained or controlled by the consortium.

The Ohio Technology Consortium is not responsible for the content of external websites. A link to a non-governmental website does not constitute endorsement.

### Contact

Any further questions concerning the privacy policy for this web site should be forwarded to the Ohio Technology Consortium webmaster via email at **webmaster (at) oh-tech.org**. Written correspondence may be sent to:

Webmaster  
Ohio Technology Consortium  
1224 Kinnear Road  
Columbus, Ohio 43212
